Okay, let's go.
Obey, four, three, two, one.
Let's make Anolab new smoothies!
Clap!
Do you guys know what a smoothie is?
I do.
I drink them all the time.
You know? You drink them all the time, right?
I get a bunch of bananas in the mail.
Bananas?
I got a mix. Let's try it all at once.
It's a sorbet-like drink made with fruits and vegetables.
I never had it when I was a kid.
What do you think?
Even as an adult, I don't drink smoothies.
Is that so?
I don't like smoothies.
When I drank a smoothie, I thought it was 100%.
I didn't know there was such a person in Japan.
100%.
Today I would like to make an original smoothie.
I would like to ask everyone to choose three ingredients.
I will mix the ingredients I choose and give them to you.
And then we will eat them together.
We'll end up drinking together.
I'll also ask you to tell me which of your friends had the best taste at the end.
How should I make it?
How should I tell my story?
Unique, stylish, and definitely good!
From here, how should I make it?
How should I make it?
by H.
I have a variety of ingredients, but I don't want to be defensive.
Defensive?
I mean, if you put apples, bananas, and oranges together, it would be delicious, no way.
You can't do that.
I don't mean that... I mean, a little bit of ginger... That's not what I meant... a little ginger or...
I can't do ginger.
He said he's going to try to match the impossible.
So let's pick the ingredients right away.
Three, right?
One from Clam's.
Any color you like.
Pick three you like.
I've dropped the names.
Yes, please choose.
Harmon, we need to get your face on the camera.
So...
I don't think that's possible.
This way, this way.
He's getting a little defensive, guys.
Okay, let's have a melon and...
Let's have one fruit.
Shall we have one fruit?
One fruit, one kind.
Melon is good.
And maybe some vegetables.
For the meal...
One set, one set.
For the camera, your face...
What is that?
Honey?
That's definitely good.
Hey, honey, they picked me.
I didn't know.
Pick three.
Pick three?
And one more vegetable.
You two are a little...
I don't have any more.
This way...
I chose.
This one? This?
What is this?
This.
It's grass. Grass.
Grass.
Hold the grass.
Okay, so these two guys have two more?
Four.
Carrots?
Okay?
That looks really bad.
Just carrots.
Just carrots, so...
Okay?
I might be able to drink carrots if I make this.
Would you like this?
Already.
What the hell.
Carrots?
Do you want carrots?
Then it's decided.
It's decided.
Okay, it's decided, it's decided.
This girl's got a really good way of choosing.
I got the chocolate.
Well, let's go ahead and announce it.
Let's announce it.
Okay, let's start with Hise-kun.
Matcha, melon and carrot.
Very aggressive.
Nice.
What do you mean?
It's just that it looks bad.
But it might taste good, so it's a very brave move.
It's a very brave move.
Okay, Harumaku. Okay, Harumaku.
What did you choose, Harumaku?
Oranges, nuts, and baked sweet potatoes.
Oh, this one, too, but I'm not sure what it is.
There's an orange.
I have a bad feeling about this. I think they're messing around.
I know, right? If it's this good, it's pretty good.
Yes, Jyunna-chan.
Grapes, eggs, and pumpkin.
Grapes, eggs, and pumpkins.
Grapes, huh?
Hey, I'm not so sure about this one either.
It's a little too much. Eggs are a bit.
Eggs are a little too hard to cook.
Are they raw?
I sometimes knob raw eggs.
Raw? You eat them raw?
I get some protein out of them.
So I'm kind of looking forward to this. I'm curious.
Nice choice.
Momoko.
Pumpkin, apple and honey.
Raw?
Isn't this good? Bears and such eat everything. It looks the best.
But, but, no honey.
What did you put it on, Misachan?
With meat-eating jiko.
Pear, spinach, and chocolate.
Oh, that's impossible.
Cocoa powder, spinach and none. Hmmm.
But the cocoa powder is too strong, and I can't taste the spinach, which I don't like.
I'm going to be crunched.
The size is different.
So it looks very tasty.
Everyone okay with veggies?
But no one put, you know, green onion or something in it.
Looks like it tastes good. Green onion.
I can't eat it. I can't do it.
Meh, this is not good.
That's right. It's bad.
It's a vegetable that people don't like.
That's right.
But as we grow up, isn't it strange that everyone can eat it, except for me?
Can you eat green peppers?
I can't eat them. I can't eat them. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
I can't eat them. No, I can't.
No, I will not eat.
I cannot eat. I can't eat.
Is it common among children?
Eggplant is eggplant.
I can't eat eggplant.
Lately, mama started serving eggplant, and I don't like it.
I received a complaint.
Mom decided to stick to the eggplant life a little bit.
Yes, so let's put them in the blender.
Hey, is this enough melon?
You know, you can't put the whole melon in.
Do you want to put melon in this?
I don't put melon.
My mom doesn't like eggplant.
Okay, now, this is Mr. Isen's selection of fruits and vegetables to be mixed.
Be careful, everyone.
Be careful.
I know.
I'll grow up soon.
It's really a knife, isn't it?
Stay away from me.
It's a knife, a knife.
Really, get away from it.
It's a knife.
That's right. I know.
That's why it feels so good.
Then it's dangerous.
Then get away from me. Okay, get away.
I'm going.
Okay, I'm going.
Whoa.
It's turning.
Again!
It doesn't look like it's going up.
Good, good, good.
Wow!
What's this?
The colors are...
Matcha powder, melon and carrot.
Don't say that.
I'll tell you.
But I can't eat all three.
I can't eat melon, carrot and matcha.
So I'm a little nervous.
I can't eat carrots.
If it's good, it'll be great, so let's try it.
Se-no!
Oh no!
Oh, no!
It doesn't taste like matcha
It doesn't taste like matcha at all!
It's so bad.
Is it good?
No, it tastes like shit.
How do you like it?
I need some water.
I want a drink.
Okay, let's just say...
Oh, it's good.
Delicious.
It's delicious.
It might taste like light chocolate, but... It might taste like light chocolate, but it's better than I expected.
It's better than I thought it would be.
It's delicious.
Okay, well, I'll keep this in mind for everyone.
I'll keep it in mind.
Hmm.
What's wrong with the color?
It's like a zero.
There's something.
This is a nut, orange, and baked potato smoothie
Nut, orange and baked sweet potato smoothie.
Shall we all drink?
I'm already drinking.
Ready?
It's stuck to me, so it won't flow.
I can't.
I'm sorry, I can't either.
Water, water, water!
Water is bad... bad... bad...
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I can't do it.
How about you, Harumaku?
You mean we can't all do it yet?
Thank you for watching.
Aren't they the same? This one.
It's the same.
The color looks like chocolate.
Where's the chocolate in this thing's appearance? It's zero, no matter what you think.
Okay, so Junna-chan chose this smoothie.
I drink so much.
It has a lot of shibo. Its really. Pumpkin, grapes and eggs.
Can I drink it now?
This is good, right?
You drank it, egg.
Let's drink it. Ready.
Grapes and eggs.
Delicious.Delicious.
Oh, I can't.
A little bit impossible.
It's good.
Oh, I can't.
I can't do it.
Impossible.
I wonder if everyone except the person who made it was able to throw up.
It's like the person I chose never moved.
You can't make it at all.
I made it myself, and I want it to be good.
How is it?
It's good.
But it's drinkable so far.
Of the three.
One, I'm hoping for these two.
Yes, I have high hopes for them. Because they are the stars of expectation.
Yes, they are.
The second one.
Thank you for your hard work.
This could be bad. Hey, what's this? Isn't it a bad color? Oh, no, no, no. This is bad.
This is probably super bad.
This is Momoko's Pumpkin, Apple and Honey Smoothie.
The color looks like curry. This is it. Like the color of curry.
Then let's eat and drink. Let's drink it.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's him. It's even him.
Oh, can you do it? Can you do it? That's great. It's a little bit.
Is it good? It's good.
I don't know. The sourness of the apples makes it hard to drink.
It's the hardest to drink.
It's the hardest. How was it? How was it when you drank it yourself?
It was really bad. It was very bad.
It's true, it's a little bit bad. Really.
Oh, yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching.
Next up, Misa chose a pear, spinach and cocoa smoothie.
I can't do spinach.
It's all bad for the smoothie industry if we don't, and right now, we're not.
This one... has cocoa in it, so that's a good thing.
I can't have spinach.
I hate spinach.
Okay.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's good.
First of all, it's the easiest to look at.
It's delicious.
This is so good.
I drank all of it.
This is spinach.
That's great.
How did you like it?
Goo!
Goo.
Well, then, let's decide on the grand prize for a bit.
I suppose you'll raise your hand with the name of the person who had the best taste.
Yes, well, the spies are kind of...
Those who said Issei-kun's was delicious
Those who said Harumaku's was delicious.
What?
Even though you were saying shit about it all those years ago?
Those who said Junna-chan's was good.
It's not bad.
Two votes.
Momoko?
Yes, ma'am.
Those who said Momoko's was good.
Then these two win the grand prix.
Who said Misa's was the best?
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
One time.
What?
Just one.
One more time.
Okay, let's try Jun-chan's.
Didn't I give you that one earlier?
One vote.
Oh, no, no, no.
I prefer Misa's.
Here you go.
Ah!
Oh!
Is your smoothie the winner, Missa?
Well, this one did.
The cocoa's kind of amazing, and the spinach and everything, it kind of takes the edge off.
How do you like it? Well, the way I feel right now, I'm glad we won.
How was it? Issei.
You were talking a lot.
If you watch YouTube, please try to make it!
That's all for now.
Let's wave to everyone!
Bye bye!
I'm feeling a little down.
Please subscribe to the Ano channel!
Thank you for watching!